(Penny:)Well, so how much is that?
About haIfway between Bruce Wayne
and Scrooge McDuck.
(Howard:)The last time we went to the zoo...
(Howard:)...that son of a bitch
made me buy him a churro.
(Leonard:)I'm sorry. I don't mean to be rude
but I need to go call Raj's sister...
(Leonard:)...who I love so much.
Ahem, so vastly much.
(Penny:)Okay, so he's got money,
and it's a few gifts, and a car.
(Howard:)And she got him
to pay off all her credit cards.
(Penny:)What? He paid off her credit cards?
Damn it, I could have dated Raj
for a couple months.
But I wouldn't have because I'm not that
kind of girl. We should really talk to Raj.
He's not gonna listen, he's in love.
(Sheldon:)Can't figure out what to do?
I remember those days.
(Sheldon:)Now if you'll excuse me, I have to...
(Sheldon:)...stay right here.
(Howard:)- This is a bad idea. We should go.
- No.